As you can see my Chrome extension has been approved and it's visible already this code looks like no users for now
But obviously we need to start to promote it
So people will know it how he is post on Twitter and
Always a tragedy for that because why not? I'm not an 80-finger speaker as well. Can you study people like a good text?
So it's a deputy
And I can ask this my extension
This is my extension
I want to promote to sub-plane promote it on Twitter
Please write a post and hashtags for me
Awesome
We added for a star so this is the screenshot. I will edit I
Will think because I think I had pinky mode. Yeah
Now he is this hey, maybe I will humanize it all I
built
Tiny Chrome is today
Okay, I can use that polish version. I have a car. I will not use emoji. It reminds me very much of aye, so
Now I can add obviously address euro. I can post an image on this. That's another post
So I will just add the image. I will go to my Chrome extension
I'll go to Chrome search or in search or I'll use the screenshot
Now this is the gift. This is the enhance your post. We've grok
But you can use this is the amundre. This is the scheduler. I think we can use this off user and scope it is
And if I go back now and open it is a clear URL
And this way we can use it
Okay
Now I can see if it works. I can see like a Twitter
extension
So maybe I will look on x I
Was search for it
Okay, we see this Chrome web store detailing
See people who recommend it above the name from
Okay, this one should work. We see it. We can try to select the most popular extension
For much downloading we can just look for people for creating it and I can post it now
And maybe as you can see we cannot edit but this way we can actually change
If it gets still nice on
It's keeping up this one more flow commission. So if we have any some views
We can try to look for other people titles
I use
Tiny Chrome extension to speed up workflow
And you can even as well like add this I build
So here's this one
I don't look like a free now I'll go to
Okay, and write it to a red post and I will copy this
We can see other extension
It should be below so people might be interested if they want and after that
What I'm going to do I will use the Twitter now I just it's option
I
Was the first one I would say
Now I can use every single build
And now I can just post it and
It should work
I will post now and besides that you can go to some of the other
Ready your post months to contain a post flare
Okay, no flare
Okay, I mean let me see this self-promotion now I can post it
And now I post it now we have to be open for criticism
But yeah, okay
Cross post into other communities. We can cross post and actually and we can add some community and I can press us in and
there are some
Possibilities to add so I would say Austin toes. It's nice and we can try to post it and
When I press it I can just use like a showcase and
Add it and if I go to Austin toes
Sent this one is like very hard to post
How quickly okay, I should just
Okay, see it now
Okay, it's a promotion. Okay, and we post in both both of the things and
I think we could post it as well in any other platforms
But keep that you might obviously that some of them do not accept if you need you want to post on like main
It will not allow you to but voice you can go to Eddie and ask him to like experts or this one
I think this is like a hub for that if old map
Can help me this like we didn't see toes promote and this is as well not so very for promotion
So the whole one the origin one is less for promoting small like
Asking question articles
This is a toe
Austin toes
some collection of awesome
And if you're interested you can try to create a boss, but it will not be so easy
So but we can still obviously just try
So if you want to maybe and it both there
change it
You can try to close promote and you see it already has free use on this where we can try to promote it on other platforms as well